https://www.rfmacdonald.com/privacy-policy/

RFMCO Announcement
R.F. MacDonald Co. to continue service to all customers impacted by the stay-at-home directives
Industrial Watertube Boilers
Heat Recovery Steam Generator (HRSG)
Employment
This Privacy Policy was last modified on Feb. 2, 2018.
R.F. MacDonald Co. (“us”, “we”, “our” or “RFM”) operates https://www.rfmacdonald.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We maintain and operate this website and are sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. Accordingly, RFM believes that you should know our online information practices, the kinds of information we may collect and how we intend to use this information.
For each visitor, we automatically collect the visitor’s domain name and/or their IP address.
If you communicate with us by email, we will collect your email address and other personally identifiable information such as your name and/or that of your employer, address and telephone number.
The information collected may be aggregated to analyze what pages visitors access, the number of visits, average time spent on the site, etc. The aggregated information is utilized to improve the design and content of the Site. Usually, the personally identifiable information we collect is used to respond to the visitor’s inquiry, but in some instances it may be used for market research or to provide you with information about our own or related goods or services that we believe support your business needs.
RFM will not sell to third parties any personally identifiable information derived from a visitor’s visit to or use of the Site.
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at the Site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our Site and customize web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
If our Privacy Policy changes or, if in the future, we intend to use information collected at the Site in a new manner not previously disclosed to you, we will post such changes on the Privacy Policy section of our Site. Only information collected after such posting shall be subject to the new Policy or will be put to the new use.
If you feel our Site is not following this Privacy Policy, please contact us immediately at 510-784-0110 and ask for the IT Department.
About Us
R.F. MacDonald Co. has been in business since 1956. We service and sell boilers, pumps and accessories for commercial and industrial applications. Our employees are full-time mechanical engineers, sales engineers, parts experts and field service personnel. Allow us to assist you in your equipment selections, installation planning, layout, permitting and project supervision.
General Engineering Contractor A-1
CA: C-4
|
NV: C-1
Contractor License
CA: #220117
|
NV: #0042816
HVAC system design requires methodical assessment of safety,
25920 Eden Landing Rd.
© 2020 R.F. MacDonald Co.
Selective Catalytic Reduction (SCR)
